Have we really broken up?
Have you really left?
I try calling, but you don't answer.
I can't forget you,
I'm falling apart.
Don't be disappointed in me for being like this.
Each day passes like tears,
Is your heart okay, my love?
Honey, oh Honey,
I miss you so much.
Whose heart is crying for you?
Honey, oh Honey,
Leave the sadness behind and live happily.
My loved one.
When I see a beautiful dress,
I keep thinking of you.
My heart feels like it's going to burst.
Each day passes like tears.
Are you truly okay, my love?
Honey, oh Honey,
I miss you so much.
Whose heart is crying for you?
Honey, oh Honey,
Leave the sadness behind and live happily.
My loved one.
Honey, oh Honey,
I miss you so much.
Don't cry in anyone's arms.
Honey, oh Honey,
Leave the sadness behind and live happily.
My loved one,
The person I love.